Family is a group of people connected by
marriage or blood.
Listen to the story.
Victor and Sarah get married.
Victor is the husband.
Sarah is the wife.
Victor and Sarah have a baby. The baby
is a boy. His name is Jason.
Victor is the baby's father.
Sarah is the baby's mother.
Baby Jason is Victor and Sarah's son.
Victor and Sarah have another baby. The
baby is a girl. Her name is Nyla.
Jason is the baby's brother.
The baby is Jason's
sister.
The baby is Victor and Sarah's daughter.
Victor and Sarah are the parents.
Jason and Nyla are the children.
30 years pass.
Jason and Nyla are adults.
Victor and Sarah are older.
Nyla gets married to Tom.
They have a baby boy, Noah, and a baby
girl, Luna.
Victor and Sarah are happy.
Victor is the baby's grandfather.
Sarah is the baby's
grandmother.
Baby Noah is Victor and Sarah's
grandson.
Baby Luna is Victor and Sarah's
granddaughter.
Victor and Sarah are the grandparents.
Noah and Luna are the grandchildren.
Now let's practice.
Listen. Is the correct picture A or B?
Mother and son.
Grandfather
and granddaughter.
Husband and wife.
Final challenge.
Read and say the name of the family
member.
Luna,
Nyla,
Victor.
Noah,
Jason.
Sarah,
remember to like and subscribe for more
English lessons.